

Sergii Kabaliuk

Date of birth: 05/08/1985

Nationality: Ukrainian

Gender: Male

CONTACT



28100 Novara, Italy (Home)



serg.arnisha@gmail.com



(+39) 3423502027



https://github.com/Stronfor

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ sergio-kabaliuk-12b707226

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

About me:

Frontend engineer with over 3 years of experience, specialising in building web apps. I have an understanding of both server and client sides of web development. Have experience with Node.js, VueJs, React and related technologies.

Key skills:

JavaScript/TypeScript, VueJS, React/Redux, Tailwind, REST APIs, node.js, npm, HTTP, MongoDB, mySQL, Git/GitHub, SPA, SSR

Proactivity, feedback loop, leading by an example, listening, supporting and mentoring people in an agile environment.

WORK EXPERIENCE

02/2023 - CURRENT Oleggio, Italy

Front-End developer Jdeal-Form srl

- Full-stack development of touch interface applications, using Node on back-end and Vue.js on the front-end side
- Debugging and optimizing apps using Chrome DevTools
- writing unit tests using Vitest

03/2018 - 05/2019 Novara

Frontend Developer - Freelance Upwork

web site frontend with XHTML

06/2016 - 08/2017 Zhytomyr, Ukraine

Frontend developer Luch srl

- javascript + jQuery plugins
- SQL DB
- bug fixing

02/2015 - 06/2016 Zhytomyr, Ukraine

- Web developer Freelance
 - website layout

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

2004 - 2009 Zhytomyr, Ukraine

Computer science European University

Address Myru Ave, 59, Zhytomyr, Ukraine

01/09/2002 - 31/05/2004 Zhytomyr, Ukraine

Technologo Zhytomyr Technological College

Address Nebesnoji Sotni St, 37, Zhytomyr, Ukraine

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Ukrainian, Russian
OTHER LANGUAGE(S): Italian | English